{
    "id": "4f9da4be64924df2a9111b76c6c223cc",
    "title": "Noun Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Your ……………………. that I lied is untrue.",
            "description": "Accusation is the noun. Accuse is a verb and accusative is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "accuse",
                "accusative",
                "accusation"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "025220f479ce426b907a0470e5f6c968"
        },
        {
            "question": "The butler received the uninvited callers with ………………………..",
            "description": "Acerbic is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "acerbic",
                "acerb",
                "acerbity"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "95b69673168c47549cc860d848f2215e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Man’s first walk on the moon was a stunning technological …………………………",
            "description": "Achievement is a noun. Achieve is a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "achieve",
                "achievement",
                "achieving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "472e2a36c36041d69dd5b49b59de9de7"
        },
        {
            "question": "His …………………………. that he stole the jewels cleared his sister of blame.",
            "description": "Acknowledge is a verb",
            "answers": [
                "acknowledge",
                "acknowledging",
                "acknowledgment"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dbfa0e50ed994963b5092c9d5cc47d63"
        },
        {
            "question": "The painting is the museum’s most recent ……………………….",
            "description": "Acquirement and acquisition are both nouns acquisition is a material possession while acquirement is a personal skill.",
            "answers": [
                "acquire",
                "acquisition",
                "acquirement"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af6303bef2d1464fa09a86760180b5d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Speaking Spanish is one of her …………………………",
            "description": "Acquirement and acquisition are both nouns acquisition is a material possession while acquirement is a personal skill.",
            "answers": [
                "acquisitions",
                "acquirements"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "812ab7e1676949308ea89a1d2e2970a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The election campaign led to bitter ………………………….. between the candidates.",
            "description": "Acrimonious is an adjective  Acrimony is the correct spelling.",
            "answers": [
                "acrimany",
                "acrimony",
                "acrimonious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81f87abac5c0428a86357842b13cf3a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put more glue on the stamp to increase its …………………………….",
            "description": "Adherence is the noun.",
            "answers": [
                "adhesive",
                "adherent",
                "adherence"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "da6bf02fdab54f1eae3950c3cd247dd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. from abroad indicates that war is about to begin.",
            "description": "Advise is a verb.  Advice is the noun.",
            "answers": [
                "Advice",
                "Advise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f1655a4715e48f2bd642d1ab4f04c85"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susan B Anthony was famed for her ………………………… of equal rights for women.",
            "description": "Advocacy means support. An advocate is a lawyer.",
            "answers": [
                "advocacy",
                "advocate",
                "advocative"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b36e442ab084bc3b55e53f047d23fda"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her finishing school accent is just an ………………………………..",
            "description": "An affectation is a false mannerism or pretense.",
            "answers": [
                "affect",
                "effect",
                "affectation"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3c6f1cfbf0544a2ebd154e4bf293a1ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am proud to pledge ………………………… to the flag and to my country.",
            "description": "Allegiance means loyalty.",
            "answers": [
                "allege",
                "allegation",
                "allegiance"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0b875e27776a4417a3d8ede720b7122e"
        }
    ]
}